Guide to the Duke Gardens Foundation records, 1912-2002 and undated
Duke University. University Archives
- Administrative Records, 1939-2002 and undated
  - Equipment estimates, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation reports and recommendations for the years 1964, 1965, 1966, 1968, and 1969, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - requests and thank yous, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Greenhouse Reports, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Vehicle #46 - 1966 International LoBoy tractor, 1966-1985 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation ledger book, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Plant material contracts, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - House #52 maintenance invoices, 1967-1989 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Reports and recommendations to Miss Duke from Duke Gardens staff, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation ledger book, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda, primarily from Miss Duke to Duke Gardens staff, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Vehicle #47 - 1968 John Deere 300 tractor, 1968-1985 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence and notes regarding exchange of plants between Somerville, N.J., and Newport, R.I., 1969 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Notes and letters from Mrs. Ethel Toburen, presumably of the Nutrition & Life Foundation, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation ledger book, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Lectures - employee training, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Garden admissions records, 1969-1970 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Garden admissions records, 1969-1970 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Papers, primarily correspondence, related to financial management, 1969-1970 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Papers, primarily correspondence, related to financial management, 1969-1970 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to daily administrative activities at Duke Gardens. Activities include salary negotiations. 1969–1970 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Admission records, 1969-1971 (1 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Admission records, 1969-1971 (2 of 2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Administrative papers of Duke Gardens Foundation related to Duke Gardens, the Foundation for South East Asian Art and Culture, and the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1969-1971 (1 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Administrative papers of Duke Gardens Foundation related to Duke Gardens, the Foundation for South East Asian Art and Culture, and the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1969-1971 (2 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Administrative papers of Duke Gardens Foundation related to Duke Gardens, the Foundation for South East Asian Art and Culture, and the Newport Restoration Foundation, 1969-1971 (3 of 3) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence relating to Universal Restoration Inc.’s reconstruction of the Italian Garden and rehabilitation of the garden and greenhouse enclosures. Diazo included. 1970 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence relating to restoration and work improvements for greenhouses, including the Persian Garden, by Lord & Burnham, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Weekly reports of Duke Gardens administration by Basil Hanger, chief horticulturist, to Doris Duke, including one accident report, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - List of Duke Gardens employees, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Administrative records regarding Duke Gardens reconstruction, including architectural records, 1970 (1 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Administrative records regarding Duke Gardens reconstruction, including architectural records, 1970 (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Legal correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, invoices, contracts, architectural drawings, and other materials relating to work contracted to Lord & Burnham, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, legal documents, and other materials related to the lawsuit Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc., versus Universal Restoration, Inc., and the Indo-Persian Garden structure, 1970-1971 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence - Carmen Cantore, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Weekly reports of Duke Gardens administration by Basil Hanger, chief horticulturist, to Doris Duke, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and other materials related to the contracting of Darryl Copeland to install lighting in the greenhouses, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and inventory regarding lighting equipment and work, 1970-1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence regarding seed and plant donations to Duke Gardens, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda from Doctor Tashjian, includes additional papers of Basil Hanger, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Bulb Cellar, includes renovation, 1970-1977 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Copies of Agreements: (1) Doris Duke and Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. (October 27, 1958); (2) The Horticultural Society of New York, Inc., and Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. (October 27, 1958), 1971 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, invoices, contracts, architectural drawings, and other materials relating to work contracted to Lord & Burnham, 1971 (1 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, invoices, contracts, architectural drawings, and other materials relating to work contracted to Lord & Burnham, 1971 (2 of 2) (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, proposals, and architectural records regarding contract work to the Indo-Persian Garden and the firm of Montrom Limited, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and promotional materials regarding fertilizers and chemicals purchased by Duke Gardens, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence and proposals regarding heat system automation with the Ventender system, including schematics, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Papers regarding waste disposal certification, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Orchid Range reports, 1971-1973 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to rehabilitation work for the Edwardian Garden and the use of plexiglass. 1971–1974 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Vehicle #1 - 1962 Buick convertible, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, notes, architectural drawings, and receipts related to renovation of Italian garden, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Duke Gardens materials regarding the S. E. A. A. C. Foundation, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence with Richard Horowitz, of Horowitz & Wirth, A. I. A., Architects and Planners, regarding design and update work to gardens, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, catalogs, and other materials from Wildlife Nurseries, Oshkosh, WI, related to growing rice on Duke Farms, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Bulbs by vendor - master totals, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Bourgondien, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Jan de Graaff, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Burnett Bros., 1972 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Bakker van Vorst, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Zanten, 1972 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, notes, architectural drawings, and receipts related to renovation of Italian garden, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Letters and architectural drawings from Lord & Burnham regarding greenhouse renovations, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, invoices, and proposals regarding heating and cooling of greenhouses, 1972-1973 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Papers related to contracts with Lord & Burnham, includes agreements and legal papers, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, memoranda, notes, and related documentation concerning improvements to the Chinese Garden (House No. 13) and the American Desert Garden (House No. 4), 1972–1975 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Contracts and legal correspondence related to greenhouses and Lord & Burnham, includes executed originals and architectural records, 1972-1976 (1 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Contracts and legal correspondence related to greenhouses and Lord & Burnham, includes executed originals and architectural records, 1972-1976 (2 of 2) (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to daily administrative activities at Duke Gardens. Topics include solicitations to produce TV commercials at Duke Gardens and permissions to take photos of the gardens. 1972–1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Vehicle #2 - 1966 Chevrolet utility truck, 1972; 1985 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Appraisals, black and white and color photographs, correspondence, receipts, and other materials related to furniture and art donations, 1972-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Agreements (copies) made between Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. and Burnham Corp. for the renovation of the Semi-Tropical, Colonial American, Tropical, Edwardian, and Italian Gardens. 1973 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Materials related to greenhouse maintenance and updates, previously labeled "French garden renovations," 1973 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Bulbs by vendor - bulb order totals and master sheet, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Driehuizen, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Bakker van Vorst, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Zanten, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Burnett Brothers, Inc., 1973 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Bourgondien, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, invoices, architectural drawings, and other materials related to ongoing greenhouse work contracted to Lord & Burnham, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence relating to upkeep of gardens and insurance risks. 1973–1980 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Letters, notes, and memoranda related to general business of Duke Gardens Foundation, 1973-1980 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Holland Flowerbulbs Sp. Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Bennett Brothers, Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Bekker van Vorst Inc., 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Bulbs by vendor - 1974 Bulb Order Total and Master Sheet, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Approvals for a feature on Duke Gardens by Architectural Digest, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Contracts and legal correspondence related to greenhouses and Roper IBG, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Flowerbulb Associates, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Bulbs by vendor- Bakker van Vorst, Inc., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons, Inc., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Holland Flowerbulbs Spec., Inc., 1975 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Bennett Brothers, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Bulbs by vendor - 1975-1976 master sheets, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Agreements and related materials concerning contractual work set for the Italian Gardens by Lord & Burnham. 1975–1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memoranda relating to renovations and repairs to the Chinese, Desert, and Edwardian Gardens. File includes select copies of Agreements and Contract documents. 1975–1981 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Chrysanthemums, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Andrew R. Kennedy, Inc., includes letter from Dutch Bulb Exporters' Association, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen B. V., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons, Inc., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bulbs by vendor - M. Van Waveren & Sons, Inc., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Bulbs by vendor- Flowerbulb Associates, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons N. V., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Bulbs by vendor- Burnett Brothers, Inc., 1976 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Vehicle #42B - 1976 GMC pick-up truck, 1976-1985 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Reports & Summaries. A compilation of trees and plants, January 1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons Inc., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Flowerbulb Associates, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Bulbs by vendor - M. Van Waveren & Sons, Inc., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons N. V., 1977 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen Limited, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Burnett Brothers, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Bulbs by vendor - general, 1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Vehicle #21 - 1945 Massey Harris tractor, 1977-1984 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Vehicle #55 - 1949 Farmall H tractor, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Vehicle #48 - International Farmall cub, 1977-1985 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Order - fuel oil #2 for homes, June 16, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Burnett Brothers, Inc., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Flowerbulb Associates, Inc., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons, Inc., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Bulbs by vendor - M. Van Waveren & Sons, Inc., 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Consent of Action in Lieu of Meeting of the Members of the Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. 1978, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Security Lights, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Vehicle #11 - 1977 International Loadstar truck, 1978-1985 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Landmarks Presentation Commission correspondence, re: Orchid Range contains report on Brooklyn Garden Palm H.S. 1979 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Burnett Brothers, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Flowerbulb Associates, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bulbs by vendor - K. Van Bourgondien & Sons, Inc., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Van Tubergen Limited, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Q. Vandenberg & Sons N. V., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Bulbs by vendor - M. Van Waveren & Sons, Inc., 1979 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Bulbs by vendor - Witteman & Co, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Major repairs - buildings and equipment, 1979-1984 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Mowers and leaf blowers, 1979-1985 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Deed between Doris Duke and Duke Gardens Foundation transferring the Orchid Range Structure to DGF. February 25, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Rental house #52 restoration plans, includes architectural records, 1980 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Restoration of House #49, includes color photographs and architectural records, 1980-1984 (1 of 2) (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Restoration of House #49, includes color photographs and architectural records, 1980-1984 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - House #52 restoration - Correspondence, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Vehicle #24 - 1959 John Deere tractor, 1980-1984 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Vehicle #77 - 1961 Farmall tractor, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Vehicle #51A - 1980 Dodge trades van, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Vehicle #31A - 1980 International diesel tractor, 1980-1985 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Restoration of House #52, including architectural records, 1980-1985 (1 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Restoration of House #52, including architectural records, 1980-1985 (2 of 2) (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - House #52 restoration, including architectural record, 1980-1986 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Rental house #52B restoration and maintenance, includes color and black and white photographs, 1980-1989 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Thank you notes, 1980, 1998, and undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Memorandum regarding the purchase of shades for the Orchid Range windows. 1981 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - New Jersey Hazardous Waste Requirements, 1981 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Papers relating to work done on Palm House by National Greenhouse Company, including contracts, correspondence, invoices, insurance policies, and canceled checks, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - House #49 - restoration paperwork, 1981-1982 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - House #79, Dutchess Farm - maintenance and repairs, 1981-1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Chrysanthemum Schedule, 1981-1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Vehicle #50 -1981 GMC truck with dump body, 1981-1996 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Insurance policies, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Vehicle #22 - 1952 Farmall H tractor, 1982-1983 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Vehicle #17 - 1953 Farmall H tractor, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Vehicle #14 - 1965 Chevrolet 3/4 ton stake truck, 1982-1984 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Vehicle #20 - 1952 Farmall tractor, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Vehicle #19 - 1955 Farmall H tractor with front end loade, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Vehicle #13 - Backhoe, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Chimney cleaning and repairs, 1982-1986 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Vehicle #84 - 1964 International Bucket cherrypicker, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and magazine articles sent by Robert Dingwall, Horticultural Consultant, regarding caring for orchids and other plants at Duke Gardens. July 31, 1983, August 16, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Motor carrier road tax paperwork, 1983-1993 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Gypsy moth spraying - Cordoba Helicopter, Inc., 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - House #52A lease - Rosalind La Roche, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Vehicle #91 - 1970 Chevrolet stake truck, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Vehicle #87 - 1984 GMC pickup, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Vehicle #86 - 1984 GMC van, 1984-1985 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Planting plan, interior gardens. circa 1985 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - New Jersey Department of Environmental Protection correspondence, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Electrical and security lighting billing - M. Gilreath, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - House #83, Dutchess Barn - maintenance, 1985-1986 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Memorandum, plants in the Main Residence. October 20, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Electrical and propane billing - M. Gilreath, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - House #52A maintenance invoices, 1986-1988 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Electrical, propane, and security light billing - M. Gilreath, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Nomination of Somerville residence to National Register of Historic Places - Ursula Brecknell, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Control Sheets - tickets, cards, and slides, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation financial reports, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Bid to reglaze greenhouses by IBG International, May 18, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Inventory of vehicles owned by Duke Gardens Foundation, July 18, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Rental houses - memoranda, unexecuted leases, and notes, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Electrical and propane billing - M. Gilreath, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Ticket season control sheet, 1988-1989 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Electrical and propane billing - M. Gilreath, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - House #3 - Boat House maintenance, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence - service providers, 1989-1997 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Blank lease for rental houses, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Damages owed and paid - Elton Dorsey (Renee Eberstadt), includes color photograph, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Maintenance Work Order Forms (blank), 1990 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Minutes of Managers Meetings, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Rental memoranda and miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Rental service agreement - Remax Realtors, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Rental house #49A - Jane M. Kugler, 1990-1991 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Damages owed and paid - Fatima Salim, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Weekly reports from Bob Storms to Miss Duke regarding vegetable production, 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Rental houses 52A - John Cunningham and Robin Richards, 1990-1994 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Rental house 52B - Marc and Kathleen Cardellia, 1990-1995 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Rental house #120 - M. Gilreath, 1990-1998 (1 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Rental house #120 - M. Gilreath, 1990-1998 (2 of 2) (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Minutes of Managers Meetings, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Utility meter readings - Rental houses 49A, 49B, 52A, and 52B, 1991-1993 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Publicity information from Rough Brothers, Inc.: Greenhouse Manufacturers, 1991-1995 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Invoice from Somerset Electrical Service, 15 January 1992 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Labs, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Minutes of Managers Meetings, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Main Growing Schedule for Duke Gardens, 1992 Oct 1-1993 May 31 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Orchid Awards and Certificates, 1992-1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - House 49A and 49B rental - Anthony and Carol Knapp, 1992-1996 (1 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - House 49A and 49B rental - Anthony and Carol Knapp, 1992-1996 (2 of 2) (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Ashland Chemical - Drew Water Services, 1992-1998 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Bek Systems, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Beneficial Insects for Orchid Range, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Donations, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Education Program, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Work and tour schedules, 1993 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Orchid Range - Donations and Assorted Donors, 1993, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - An-Tec Labs/Virus Testing, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Minutes of Managers Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Schedule for Seeding & Display Gardens, 1993-1994 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Orchid Donations - Woodstream/Goldner, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Rental properties, 1993-1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Clippings related to Doris Duke's estate, 1993, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Xerox - equipment purchase, warranty, and maintenance, 1993-1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Consent to Action In Lieu of 1994 Annual Meetings of the Sole Member and Sole Director of the Duke Gardens Foundation, Inc. February 18, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Combustion Chamber work bid from James McDougall & Sons, Inc., July 1994 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Poly Growers Greenhouse Co. brochure, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Periodical subscriptions, 1994-1996 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Insurance - assault and battery exclusion, January 9, 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - American Protective Services, Inc. - monitoring system, 1995-1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Hillsborough Township fire safety inspection reports, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda, reports, invoices, and other materials related to general administration, 1995-1997, 2001 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - MobileComm papers, 1995-1998 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Ticket season control sheets, 1995-1997 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Control sheets by month - cards, slides, reels, and viewers, October-December 1996 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Monthly ticket control sheets, October-December 1996 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Tour reservation schedules, October-December 1996 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Inventory - Administration Building, November 23, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - AT&T telephone bills, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - House #9 rental, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Sprayer, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Advance deposits - lists and transmittal letters for garden tours, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Letters and invoice regarding damages made by Siemens (Rolm) employees, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Hewlett Packard LaserJet, 1996-1998 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence and clippings related to Duke Gardens advertising, 1996-2000 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Report - Duke Gardens staff and description, February 1, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Duke Gardens Foundation Annual General Ledger, December 31, 1997 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Control sheets by month - cards, slides, reels, and viewers, January-May 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Monthly ticket control sheets, January-May 1997 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Tour reservation schedules, January-March 1997 (Box 27, Folder 5)